Hello everyone! This is Hitomi Takamatsu and Shioko Akiaki from Equal Love!
Hi everyone! So today, we have a hamburger club!
Yay! Finally!
We usually go out to eat hamburgers together, and we've been having a lot of fun!
We called it “Equal Love Hamburger Club”.
We planned it on our own.
We've been doing it on our own, and we've already done it quite a few times.
But then, this time
This time, we're going to be an official club activity of the Ikorabuhanberger Club on the Mai J Channel.
We're going to film one of them for the time being!
Thank you very much!
New release! I'm so happy!
Isn't it great?
I'm so happy! I'm so glad I went.
I'm glad I went to so many.
I'm glad we went a lot.
I'm the only one.
Great!
So today, we are here at Omotesando!
Today we are at a hamburger shop called “Kyokuburger” in Omotesando!
Yay!
First time, right?
First time!
First time here!
First time here.
Yeah!
It's so stylish.
Yeah.
And today, it's like a private project.
It's just a time to enjoy a delicious hamburger!
Yay!
It's so good!
It's great!
Five views, right?
Five!
Well, I'm going to pick a menu today!
Look! LOOK!!!
Burgers & premium steaks too!
Great!
I'm going to go there!
Wow, what a variety of food they have!
Wow!
Oh, wow!
I like the cheeseburger.
We usually get the cheeseburger.
Cheeseburgers all the time.
Even with toppings.
Yes, cheeseburger with cheese as a topping.
Cheese topping.
Oh, my God!
Wait, what?
Is this bad?
Cheese?
Fluffy Gouda cheese!
Just a little...
It's...
It's good, right?
It says “Rolex” on it.
This far?
So far?
It looks like Omotesando.
Hey!
Oh, this!
I've seen this! I've seen this!
BLT cheeseburger...
I had to check it out.
This is on it.
I think this might have been on there.
We're always so confused. We're always so confused.
I know.
It's true.
You can't make a decision by yourself. You can't decide alone for the rest of your life.
You know, I end up with half a dozen or something.
That's why I gave you the picture of the two of us.
I thought we were eating one at a time.
But we always order different menus while having half of the meal.
But we always order different menus.
So, do you want to do that this time, too?
You want to?
Yeah. - Okay.
Well... wait, I like the toppings today.
Dicing.
There's cheese, there's bacon.
Okay.
Okay, so we're going to have
Double Kobe Beef Cheeseburger and the BLT Cheeseburger.
BLT cheeseburger.
That's fine.
I feel like a cheeseburger.
And the passet?
Passet?
Or a set.
A set?
I'm going to order a set.
Yay!
Thank you for watching.
Poppin' folks, you're gonna love it.
Please put on your broads, cut your burgers, and serve with your choice of sauce.
I'm saying it's a Reynolds Mark... I've never worn gloves before and I've never worn a skill set before.
Look at this bat. You can put it on a sprayer and cut it off.
Look at this bat. You can put it on the sprayer and you can cut it off.
But everyone wears black gloves to eat. We wear black gloves, too.
Yu, beautiful. Smells good.
Oh, it smells so good!
Oh, my God, they're almost here.
I want to see what's downstairs. Excuse me, excuse me, the double Kobe beef and cheeseburgers. I'd like to take a look downstairs. Excuse me, excuse me, I'd like a double corbe beef and cheeseburger, please.
Excuse me, sir.
What's this?
I'll eat it myself.
Quail eggs!
It's a self-cut quail egg, but please eat it in this sauce.
It's absolutely delicious!
Oh, no!
What's this?
Cut it off.
That's amazing!
Oh, my God, I've never done that before.
Hey, hey, buns.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, they're so thick.
Here we go.
I've never worn gloves before.
Black gloves.
Bon appétit.
Oh, my God.
What?
Huh?
Oh, the bread is crispy!
Oh, wait, it looks so good!
This is too good to be true!
It's too good to be true!
Next, pizza!
Pizza!
Pizza is ready!
Wait, it's huge!
It's huge.
Oh, my God. That's great.
Totally different sizes.
Then I'll eat it with it.
I think I'll try one as it is.
Certainly.
Bon appétit!
Mmm
Oh, wow.
It's so stretched. The cheddar cheese is stretched.
It's so good. Oh, my God.
I'm gonna dip it in.
Each one looks like a completely different sauce. They taste so different.
Mmm! Sweet!
Yummy!
Too good!
What do we do now?
Oh, no!
Oh, no! I'm gonna lose him.
It's so good!
Sweet.
Ya!
Fresh! New sensation!
Until now.
I used to put the burger in a piece of paper
and eat it on a pile of paper.
But now it's possible!
It's fun and delicious!
What if this is
The Equal Love
L
L at Equal Love
L for Equal Love
How is it?
Good?
Looks good. Looks delicious.
I want some of that too.
Tiny.
Crunchy!
Daioikai Special!
I'll try the other tooth.
I'll try it.
Bon appétit!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's totally different! Delicious! They're both delicious!
Wow! You were right to put avocado in there!
I could seriously put avocado in anything!
You really did the right thing by putting avocado in the BLT burger!
I'm going to buy a camera and make the right decision!
I'll put it in there!
Yes! Lots of cheese!
Delicious!
I think this BLT is more like a burger for the newbie burger lover, and I think it tastes even better.
This double cheeseburger is a hamburger! Meat! I want to eat it! I love hamburgers!
I love burgers!
Yes!
It tastes good!
I'm really good at cutting.
I'm so good! It's all falling apart on me.
You really should see it.
I'm really good! I did a really good job!
Mmm! Yummy!
Oh, no! It's falling over! It's tipping over! It's too good!
Whenever we eat a hamburger, people always tell us how we can eat it all.
We can! All the time!
I'm sure I'll end up with dessert!
This is also quite a large portion, so you can share it between two people.
Or you can order one hamburger and one hamburger!
You can enjoy it in many ways!
Have you ever split one of these?
No, I have not!
No?Do you have any?
Egg Corner!
Let's try cracking open a bowl!
Go!
Oh, my gosh!
So beautiful!
Yum!
Yeah!
That's great!
You did it so well!
It's absolutely delicious!
It's good, right?
Okay!
Tomi will try to crack it open.
I'm afraid it won't work.
It's okay, it's okay.
What's this?
I'm in dance form.
You have a cute body.
Why can't you even do this right? I'm cute.
I'm cute... with a heart.
Can we just call it an Equal Love thing?
I can do it. I can do it.
I'm drinking quail for the first time in my life.
It's not coming out.
I guessed it! That's good.
It worked.
I'm so clumsy.
It just happened.
Here we go. Eggs.
No? Taste.
No. A little different.
It's mellowed out.
Eat it.
Mellow.
You can still taste it.
It's a little different. It's a little different.
Tastes like something your kids would like.
It's good.
It's delicious.
I love it when you can change it up.
Bread burgers...
I'm worried about getting my hands dirty.
But if you put this on...
I can eat whatever I want.
I love this style!
I'll bring it from now on.
The carbonation in the express is too loud!
It's divine!
It's delicious too!
But I don't like spicy food
I don't like spicy food.
You don't like spicy food?
I am.
What?
You don't like spicy food?
Can you take it?
Yes, I can.
It's good.
Spicy.
It's spicy.
It's hot after the first bite.
Isn't this spicy?
It's not spicy?
I thought you didn't like spicy food?
I don't like spicy food.
I can handle spicy sensations.
It's not spicy at first bite?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's really spicy.
Spicy.
Spicy. It's hot.
The smell was spicy.
painful
spicy
Spicy
I'm scared of my mouth
It's like I'm being punished that much.
It's really spicy.
But let's eat it.
It's delicious.
Delicious!
Thank you for the food.
Yes, so, thank you very much for the food!
I ate all of it!
It was too delicious!
I'm so full!
I also got the staff's Kyokuen burger, and now we're both in the middle of a fire!
My whole body is on fire!
If you eat the Kyokuen Burger, please be careful with the spiciness of the burger!
And, I don't know if this hamburger club will continue, but I'd like to introduce to you the hamburger shop that allowed us to come here.
What do you call it?
Let's put a catch phrase on this hamburger shop!
The “pole” of this “Kyoku Burger” is the “pole” of the hamburger district.
Yes, that's correct.
Yes, hand shoes.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Pole Burger is...
Could you please explain a little bit?
KYOKU BURGER's is the pole of poles, so the restaurant's catchphrase is
The pole of the hamburger world
Yay!
It's decided!
Let's call it “Pole of the burger world”!
No, it really was the pole, wasn't it?
It was so much fun!
It was fun, wasn't it? It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I've never had so much fun eating a polar bear burger.
I don't know.
From the moment I came out, I was in the glove room.
It was so much fun, I didn't even have to worry about getting dirty, I could just go for it!
I'm going to end today, but if your feedback is good, I'm sure I'll see you again at the Hamburger Club somewhere else.
Please give us a good button and a high rating!
Thank you!
I thought we were the same.
OK.
Please click “Good” button, subscribe to our channel, and comment!
Please do!
Seriously, I know this video is kind of a loosely private one, but...
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!